本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译制作仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为若因私自散布传播造成法律问题 本字幕组概不负责更多影视请搜索并关注新浪微博@大家字幕组
在成功对约旦和埃及进行国事访问后
After successful visits to Jordan and Egypt,
大家字幕组
m 16 2 l 3 8 l 12 8 l 12 6 l 16 6 m 33 -5 l 37 8 l 42 8 m 29 -12 l 21 -12 l 24 -10 l 24 6 l 23 8 l 30 8 l 25 -5 l 27 -10 l 31 -10 m -15 -5 l -23 8 l -7 8 m -9 -12 l 12 -12 l 2 -8 l 2 -4 l 13 -9 l 15 -7 l 2 -1 l 2 2 l 16 -4 l 16 -2 l 2 4 l 1 6 m -11 -24 l 15 -24 l 15 -22 l 1 -22 l 1 -16 l 11 -16 l 11 -19 l 25 -19 l 28 -15 l -11 -15 m -20 -22 l -24 -15 l -20 -15 m -26 -12 l -21 -12 l -32 6 l -33 6 l -33 8 l -39 8
EVERYONE
大家字幕组
Meyer总统的中东和平之旅
President Meyer's Middle East peace tour
将在以色列继续展开
Continues with her trip to Israel.
刚刚失去工作的时候 负面影响会持续一段时间
You lose your job, you're radioactive for a while.
规则就是这样
That's just how it works.
大家字幕组
是的 我会照顾好自己的 妈妈
Yes, I am taking care of myself, mother.
没有 我没给她寄早日康复卡
No, I didn't send her a get-well card
因为人们不会因为做整形手术收到早日康复卡
'cause you don't get a get-well card when you have plastic surgery.
我得挂了
I've got to go.
因为我要出去跑一圈
'Cause I'm-- I'm going for a run.
好的 再见
Okay, bye.
我已经决定在以色列多呆一天
...I've extended my stay in Israel for another day.
所以我可能需要借一些牙膏
So I may need to borrow some toothpaste.
翻译：埃可博 坑坑 鑫鑫
翻译：rebecca 糖佩斯 惊鸣
轴：Liber 压制:天天
校对:xz 天然绯 埃可博
副总统
第四季 第四集
Meyer总统在她十天出访的最后
President Meyer has ended her 10-day world tour
意想不到地访问了伊朗
With a surprise visit to Iran.
她的这次历史性会面
Her historic meeting
可能使双方数十年来的不信任即将结束的信号
Could signal an end to decades of mistrust.
看到这次访问了吗？ 是我安排的
See that tour? I set that up.
看到那个架子了吗？ 是我做的
See that shelf? I made that.
可以相信Meyer总统还会确保释放
It's believed President Meyer may also secure the release
被扣押的美国记者Leon West
Of detained American reporter Leon West.
这次出访简直是个奇迹
This trip is like a miracle.
那个改变国际政局的女人哪去了
Where's the woman who changed world politics?
- 她去撒尿了 - 她去梳洗了
- She's taking a piss. - She's freshening up.
“出自I‘m so hungry, I could eat a horse”
我困得前胸贴后背能生吞一匹马
I'm so tired, I could sleep a horse.
已经口不择言了
Or whatever that word thing is.
等等 Ben 这不是安眠药吗？ 你吃了多少啊？
Wait, Ben, is this Ambien? How many of these have you taken?
我需要睡觉
Look, I need to sleep.
我昨天晚上甘草精吃多了
I got all jacked up on licorice last night
肚子里面一直翻滚 直到天亮
And I was belly dancing till dawn.
- 现在能去接Leon了吗？ - 哦 我问问
- Is it time to get Leon yet? - Oh, checking.
试想一下被扣押两个星期
Imagine being detained for two weeks
就因为你是个记者和白痴
Just 'cause you're a journalist and a shithead.
是啊
Yeah.
让我们与他被扣押的事摆脱关系 干的不错啊
It's a good job we had nothing to do with his being detained.
是啊 那样的话就完蛋了
Yeah, wouldn't that be terrible?
等等 这件事与我们有关？
Wait, did we have something to do with...?
哦耶 哦耶 你最好欢呼
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, you better cheer
因为我是最棒的总统
For the president of the year.
耶！
Yeah!
- 嘿 你知道你是谁吗？ - 什么？
- Hey, you know what you are? - What?
- 你是个了不起的人 - 谢谢
- You're an amazing man. - Thank you.
- 你知道了不起的人会得到什么吗？ - 什么？
- And you know what amazing men get? - What?
- 周末两天假 - 这个周末吗？
- Two-day weekend. - This weekend?
- 是啊 - 我要和Wendy去我们的小屋！
- Yeah. - I'm going to the cottage with Wendy!
哦 他们还要再扣押Leon一个小时
Oh, they're detaining Leon for one more hour.
哦 天啊 我还得在这等一个小时才能起飞吗？
Oh, god. I have to wait here another hour before we can fly out?
你得和Leon West照张照片 女士
You have to get a photo with Leon West, ma'am.
- 是啊 -  只有这个时候才会有人这样说
- Yeah. - It's the one and only time anyone's ever gonna say that.
这一小时我们得干点什么事 对吗？
Let's use the hour, then, okay?
我们来治愈糖尿病 或者学会意大利语
Let's cure diabetes or learn Italian.
您为什么不去打个盹呢？
Why don't you take a nap?
你在开玩笑吗？ 我这辈子都不会睡觉了
Are you kidding? I'm never gonna sleep again.
我要像拉布拉多犬那样绕圈跑
I gotta run around like a Labrador
或者像着了火的人一样 或者其他什么的
Or a guy on fire or something like that.
伊朗 伊朗啊！ 是不是太让人难以置信了？
Iran. Iran! Isn't that amazing?
哦 我得再去趟洗手间 马上就回来
Ooh, I've got to go to the bathroom again. I'll be right back.
- 哇哦 她好激动啊 - 她简直疯了
- Wow, she's excited. - She's fucking nuts.
媒体专机上的人怎么样了？
How are the folks on the press plane?
还没醉
Sober.
酒瘾一上来他们抖得太厉害 我觉得飞机都开始摇晃了
They got the shakes so bad, I think I see the plane rattling.
你得去告诉他们我们还要等一个小时
Well, you've got to tell them we got to stay another hour.
一个小时？ 这些人急了能把飞机燃油给喝了
An hour? These guys could be drinking jet fuel.
喔 让开
whoa, out of my way!
是个假警报 我不知道为什么
It was a false alarm. I don't know why.
嘿 女士 要不要我给您按摩按摩肩膀什么的？
Hey, ma'am, why don't I give you a shoulder massage or something?
会帮助您放轻松 分散您的注意力 - 不！
- It'll kind of help you unwind, defocus. - No!
我不要分散注意力 我要集中注意力
I don't want to defocus. I'm all focus.
我现在能用我的眼光钉一根钉子在墙上
I could, like, bang a nail into that wall with my gaze.
你们懂吗？ 你开心吗？
Do you know what I mean? You having fun?
- 是的 -你开心吗？
- Yes. - Are you having fun?
- 太开心了 - 这个桌子是什么木头做的？
- So much fun. - What kind of wood is this table?
- 不知道 我来看看 -我觉得这是白蜡木
- I don't know. Let me check. - I think it's ash.
我要重新装修我的厨房
I'm gonna redo my kitchen.
女士 您真的认为这个时候需要考虑这些事情吗？
Ma'am, you think you want to think about this right now?
是啊 当然 我们现在有时间啊
Yeah, sure. I mean, we've got time.
- 我们有一个小时的时间 - 是吗？ 好吧
- We've got an hour. - Do we? Okay.
我要换全新的橱柜
I'm gonna get all new cabinets.
要和这个相称 只是我不喜欢这些纹理
And I want to match this except I don't like these knots.
由于总统的出访延长一天
Now that the president's tour has been extended by a day,
总统的一些工作安排将由副总统代理
The vice president will be picking up part of the president's schedule
首先是彩红衫活动
Starting with the Rainbow Jersey event
支持体育界的所有性取向
Supporting all sexualities in sports
和NBA球星Freddy Wallace一起 请提问
With NBA star Freddy Wallace. Yes?
你对参议员O'Brien的这个评论如何回应……
How do you respond to Senator O'Brien's comment--
美国人民需要的是一个总统 而不是一个真主Meyer 好吗?
That the American people need a president, not a Meyertollah?
这是一个很低级的外号 真的很希望……
It's a cheap pun, so absolutely expect...
- 这结尾的一句真是…… - 令人恼怒？ 是的
- That finishing sentences thing is... - Irritating? Very.
不过这在当人们迟缓蠢钝的时候非常必要
But sometimes necessary when people are being slow or dull.
- 请提问 - Mike什么时候回来？
- Yes? - When's Mike back?
很搞笑 干得好
Hilarious. Well done.
没有人类的技能 像一个机器人
No people skills. Like a robot.
嗯
Hmm.
……被扣押的记者Leon West的背景信息？
Of the detained us journalist Leon West?
媒体专机
伊玛目霍梅尼国际机场
同志们 很抱歉要延迟起飞
Guys. Guys. Sorry about the delay.
事实证明 伊朗人的所有东西都要一式三份
Turns out the Iranians need everything in triplicate.
也许这就是他们发明数字的原因 对吧
Maybe that's 'cause they invented numbers, huh?
- Leon现在怎么样了 - 他很好
- How's leon doing? - He's fine.
他们随时可能会释放他
They're releasing him any minute.
我们接受吧 有人可能会因为这件事找他出书呢
Let's face it, he's probably gonna get a book deal out of this.
看到没有？ 猫一样的反应力
See that? Catlike reflexes.
哦 最好不要喝酒……
Oh, and maybe don't start drinking...
- 接着 - 等到飞机起飞再喝
- Heads up! - ...Till you're up in the air
出于对于东道国的礼貌
Out of courtesy to our host nation.
让酒吧开放吧！
Just open the bar!
很高兴与你们谈话
Great chatting.
哇哦 Freddy Wallace
Wow, Freddy Wallace.
名人堂成员 NBA的同性恋先生
Hall of Famer. Mr. Gay NBA.
在我家里 篮球是一种信仰
In my family, basketball is a religion.
当然天主教也是
Also Catholicism.
事实上那才是主要的信仰
That's actually the main one.
哦 嗨 你们能弄到Freddy的亲笔签名吗？
Oh, hey, guys. Can you get Freddy's autograph?
- 我朋友的儿子想要 - 让他签给谁？
- It's for my friend's son. - Who should he make it out to?
- Sue Wilson 他按我的名字起的名 - 哦
- Sue Wilson. He's named after me. - Oh.
- 发言稿吗？ - 是的 先生
- Is this the speech? - Yes, sir.
- 不会有纰漏吧 - 不会 没问题
- Any snags? - No, all good.
先生 Freddy Wallace可能会用到LGBT这个词
Sir, freddy wallace may use the term LGBT.
我这样记这个词的 L代表打网球的女人们
I remember it this way-- L is for ladies who play tennis,
G代表上别的男人们的男人们
G is for guys who do other guys,
B代表双性恋 我想不出这个怎么记
B is for bisexual-- I couldn't think of one to go for that--
t呢--是代表大吃一顿或者塞点儿什么
And t-- is for tucking it in or tacking it on.
其实是指跨性别者
it's transgender, actually.
谢谢你终结了我的玩笑 还让它面目全非
Thanks for killing my joke and then mutilating it.
好吧 就像我爷爷永远不会说的
Well, as my grandfather never said,
让我们去包罗世界万象吧
Let's go be inclusive.
你们看过Kent的得票了吗?
Have you seen Kent's polling?
我真是可爱到不能再可爱了
I could not be more likable
如果我把我的俩肾捐给生病的小孩儿的话
If I had given both of my kidneys to some sick kid.
我三姨妈的七舅老爷啊!
god almighty!
Gary 我想来点儿香槟
Gary, I want some champagne.
嗯呃 女士 我们现在可是在茶道至上的地方
Mm-hmm. Ma'am, we're in a tea totalitarian state.
看看这些数字 我一直在盯着呢
Look at these numbers. I keep staring at them.
我要把它设成屏保 你是怎么设的
I'm gonna make this, like, a screensaver. Wonder how you do that.
彩虹战衣告诉我们是不可以有歧视的
The rainbow jersey shows that there's no place for discrimination
法庭内外都一样
Either on or off the court.
我很高兴总统--
And I'm proud to have the president--
抱歉 副总统...
I'm sorry, the vice president...
...是和我一伙的
...On my team.
- 你的苏打水 - 谢谢
- Sparkling water. - Thank you.
我把香槟倒在瓶子里了
I put the champagne in the water bottles.
- 你不用解释 我能看出来 - 是啊
- You don't have to explain. I can tell what you did. - Yeah.
噢 你们看看Doyle
Oh, look at doyle.
他是戴过牙套了吗? 哦 额滴神啊
Did he have his teeth capped? Oh, my god.
最后一个幸存的金发女郎
The last surviving golden girl.
差点就把他送进禁区
Almost put him in the penalty box for that,
不过那是曲棍球 所以...
But that's hockey, so...
我要说几句
I'm gonna say a little something.
这最开始不是写给总统用的吗?
Wasn't this originally written for potus?
演讲就是演讲
A speech is a speech.
音位变换组合以产生意义
Phonemes connecting to produce meanings.
运动能把我们聚在一起
Sports can bring us together,
结束对同性恋的憎恶
Help end homophobia.
当我还是个...小男孩的时候
When I was a... Boy,
是我的男同朋友们
It was my gay friends
教会了我如何容忍他人
Who taught me how to be tolerant
如何直面你自己
And how to be true to yourself
还有如何跟麦当娜跳舞
And how to dance to madonna.
- 麦当娜? - 什么鬼?
- Madonna? - What?
我是要说这个来着吗?
was I supposed to say that?
你造 在大学时 我的...
You know, back in college, my...
女朋友会--男朋友--我的朋友...
Girlfriends would-- boyfriends-- my friends...
或许是该重新写写来着
Perhaps it did need some reworking.
德黑兰 纳沙德机场酒店
谢谢你的帮忙 Abbas
Thank you so much for your assistance, abbas.
他们把那记者带出去了
They're bringing the journalist out.
- 他是你朋友吗? - Leon吗? 噢 天哪 才不是
- Is he a friend of yours? - Leon? Oh, god, no.
他是傻逼中的战斗逼
He is the asshole of an asshole's asshole.
我对那些要带他走的兄弟们表示抱歉
I feel bad for the guys who had to guard him.
- Mike - Leon
- Mike. - Leon.
你这张我永远不想亲的脸
A face I never thought I'd want to kiss.
- 现在依然不想 - 宾馆不错吧?
- I still don't. - Nice hotel?
还不错 我会在"旅行家"上写点儿什么夸夸它
Yeah, I'll have something to say about it on tripadvisor.
- 有史以来最差劲的酒柜 - 以及其他东西 是的
- Worst minibar ever. - Amongst other things, yeah.
噢 这是Abbas 我们的联络人
Oh, this is abbas, our liaison.
- 这是Leon West - 很抱歉 West先生
Leon west. Apologies, mr. West.
两国都延期了这次会晤
Both countries had to deny the visit,
不过现在我们确定了
But now we confirm.
等等 两国?
Wait, both countries?
啊 他英语不是很好
Uh, his english isn't very good.
我还是能听得懂的
It sounded fine to me.
至于你 先生 准备好坐空军一号飞回家吧
And you, sir, get to fly home on air force one.
- 哇哦 - 是的
- Whoa. - Yeah.
我要是因为这个激动是不是太肤浅了
I'm shallow enough for that to be exciting.
你知道它连核爆炸都不怕吗?
Did you know it can survive a nuclear blast?
- 是啊 - 知道
- Yeah. - Yeah.
除非你的手下准备这么炸一下
Not that you guys are planning one.
我--无视我吧 我也不知道为啥我要说这个
I-- ignore me. I don't know why I said that.
他的英语也不是很好啊
His english isn't very good.
那么 我们走吧
well, let's get you going.
总统准备了一大杯加冰苏格兰威士忌给你
The president has a big-ass scotch on the rocks for you.
- 不错 - 其实就是加了冰的茶 冰茶
- Yeah. - Which is iced tea. It's iced tea.
- 谢谢你 Abbas - Mike
- Thank you, abbas. - Mike.
谢谢你
Thank you.
- 旅途安全 - 你留在这也要安全
- Safe trip. - Safe stay.
那么 让我们来庆祝一下我和我的团队所取得的成就
So let's celebrate all things l and gbt.
好吗?
Huh?
在LGBT基础上加上了queer(对自身性别不认同的人)
不过现在我们用了更具包容性的LGBTQ
Though these days we use the more inclusive lgbtq.
确实!
We do!
呃 我...
Um, and I...
尊重所有人做q的权利(其实他是不懂在胡扯)
Respect all people's rights to be a q.
或者不只是q
Or rather just q.
是啊 只是q
Yeah, just q.
他听起来像是在学习性别表一样
Sounds like he's learning a sex alphabet.
我曾见过北美灰熊嘴里的大马哈鱼
I've seen a salmon in a grizzly's mouth
都没有他这个恐怖啊
Look less panicky than that.
大家都知道q意味着有问题的
Everybody knows that q means questioning.
讽刺的是 直男们
Ironically, the straight guy
对同性恋们的认识十分僵化
Is very stiff around the gay guy.
我们的投票显示他更被广泛地认为成
Our polling said that he was widely perceived
老古板
As quite wooden.
你为什么要投票给他?
Why were you polling him?
我投给他是为了反对那些潜在的竞选对手
I was polling him against other potential running mates.
- 向后退! - 我可不是个倒着走的人 Amy
- Just move! - I'm not a backwards walker, amy.
总统向Doyle保证他会出现在选票上
The president promised doyle he'd be on the ticket
她不会投其他可能的竞选对手的票
And she wouldn't poll other possible running mates.
没人跟我说过这些
No one told me that.
又一次 左手完全不知道右手在干嘛
Yet again, the left hand has no idea what the right hand is doing
而畸形的第三只手
And the freakish middle
一下下打在我胸口上
hand is punching me repeatedly in the tits.
好吧 那是个教训
Well, that was an education.
我是说 我真正想做的是去政治游说
I mean, what I really want to do is get into lobbying.
不过已经过去了 大概
But it's only been, like,
四十五天 所以我再也不对它抱有幻想了
six weeks and three days, so I'm not sweating it.
哦 别挂 我有个电话进来
Oh, hold on. I got another call.
Sidney 嗨! 太好玩了
Sidney, hey! It's so funny.
我刚刚还在跟一个朋友说政治游说--
I was literally just commenting to a friend about lobb--
是 没错 一点也不好玩
Yeah, you're right, that's not interesting.
是的 我很想加入
Yes, I would love to come in.
所以这就是PKM
So this is pkm.
PKM - Sidney Purcell的办公室
这地方也太大了
This place is huge.
是啊 等你看到海豚馆再说
Yep. Wait till you see the dolphinarium.
就在拉丁部旁边
It's right near the latin quarter.
他还有一块了红灯区
And he's got the red-light district.
天哪 这地方太奇妙了
God, this place is so awesome.
我有点儿看上它了
I kind of feel like hitting on it.
好吧 这儿的女人你可以随便看 如果你想的话
Well, there's women here you can do that to if you wanted.
我注意到了 哦 那么 丹 这是我的筹码
I noticed. Oh. So, dan, here's my pitch.
我能让你变得富有
I can make you so rich,
富得能让比尔盖茨在你大腿上跳舞
you can pay bill gates to give you a lap dance.
让我听听你的筹码吧
Let me hear your pitch.
好吧 我很聪明 人脉很广--
Well, I'm smart, well-connected--
而且是被炒了的 对 别忘了你是被解雇的
And fired. Yeah, don't forget fired.
-之所以被炒 -哦 好吧
- Fired up... - Oh, okay.
是为了让我的各种关系为你的客户服务
To put my contacts to work for your clients.
哦 这对我的钱包来讲就是妙音啊
Well, that's music to my wallet.
不过你准备好了在Mike Mclintock的门阶上拉屎吗？
But are you ready to take a dump on Mike McLintock's doorstep?
这是入帮仪式之类的吗？
Like an initiation kind of thing?
不是 我说的是 你能接受你的客户们
No, I mean, can you take on clients
都将会因为你捣乱Meyer总统的计划而受益吗？
who are best served by you shitting on the Meyer agenda?
哦 让我想想
Oh, well, let me think about that.
-好啊 当然了 -很好
- Yeah. Yeah. - Great.
我们过段时间再来谈这个门阶拉屎的事
We'll get to that doorstep thing later, though.
好啊 我还是想那么做的 我喜欢干这事
Yeah, I'll still do that. I'm into it.
女士 请允许我向您介绍这一小时的英雄
Ma'am, may I present the hero of the hour
和您一样是英雄
along with yourself.
欢迎登上空军一号
Welcome aboard Air Force One.
-谢谢 女士 -哦 天啊 哦
- Thank you, ma'am. - Oh, gosh. Oh.
好吧 我们还要抱着吗？
Okay, are we still doing it?
好的 很好 是的
Okay. Great, yeah.
-他需要除臭剂 -好的
- He needs deodorant. - Uh-huh.
那么 很开心能见到你 Leon
Well, I am so happy to see you, Leon.
为了你能被释放 我们真的是很拼命啊
We really did work tirelessly for your release.
谢谢您 总统女士 这段时间我其实没怎么睡觉
Well, thank you, Madam President. I haven't slept very much.
哦 我很肯定食物是你脑子中所想的最后一样东西
Well, I'm sure food is the last thing on your mind.
我知道这是我想的最后一样东西
I know it's the last thing on my mind.
-我想知道你是不是饿了 -是的 我饿了
- I wonder if you're hungry, though. - Yes, I am.
因为我要告诉你 这次中东之旅
Because I'll tell you something, the adrenaline
身上产生的肾上腺素使我不需要吃任何东西
on this Mideast trip has just kept me from eating anything.
你刚刚是不是说你确实想吃点东西
Did you just say you do want something to eat?
-是的 谢谢 -是的
- Yes, thank you. - You do?
-哦 那是食物吗？-不是
- Oh, is that food? - No.
这 这是除臭剂
It's a... It's deodorant.
呃
Huh. Uh...
呃 好吧
Uh, all right.
你想吃点什么？
What would you like to eat?
除了鹰嘴豆 都可以
Anything that's not chickpeas.
嘿 为什么这两条可爱的长腿要从我身边走开？
Hey! Why are those lovely long legs walking away from me?
说的应该是你吧
Probably means you.
是的 没关系 我来搞定
Yeah, it's okay. I got... I got this.
我不是推卸责任 但是这次彩虹色的
I am not in the blame game, but that rainbow-colored
大灾难完全就是你的错
clusterfuck in there was entirely your fault.
喔 好的 不要 Kent Davison为其他副总统候选人做了民意调查
Whoa, okay, no. Kent Davison polled other candidates for veep.
搞什么？ 你刚才是想
What the fuck? Did you just
把Kent拉下水来救你自己吗？
throw Kent into the blender to save your own ass?
也不是完全拉下水
Not fully into the blender.
也许只是拉了一点点 就只是脚趾 因为……
Maybe just a little bit. Just the toe, 'cause...
这才是你到这儿后
That is the Jonah I've been
我一直试图唤醒的Jonah嘛
trying to wake up since the day you got here.
Kent Davison是个不忠诚的混球
And Kent Davison is a disloyal fucking prick.
我他妈可讨厌Kent了
I fucking hate Kent.
我特想把他脸上那副中立的表情抹掉
I want to wipe that neutral expression off his face.
我们这样做 好吧？
- Here's how we're gonna do it. - Okay.
我们泄漏出副总统现在很不满意
We're gonna leak that the VP is dissatisfied
他想退出的消息
and that he's thinking of walking.
我们要逼总统来支持Doyle
We're gonna force POTUS to back Doyle.
我不会让你失望的
I will not let you down.
好的 那么你在媒体里有哪些熟人？
All right, so what kind of media contacts do you have?
-Liz Kerrigan  -Liz吗？
- Liz Kerrigan. - Liz?
-Liz -你和这个Liz关系有多硬？
- Liz. - How hard can you work this Liz?
哦 天啊 硬到我可以把她操到汁水四溢
Oh, my God. I can ride her hard, hang her up wet.
我喜欢你现在的表现 好吧？
I like what I'm seeing, all right?
-多多展现自己啊 -谢谢 我会的
- Show me more. - Thank you, I will.
-在这下面放两个桶 -噢!
- Give 'em both barrels. - Oh!
简直是他妈的噩梦
Fucking nightmare.
这真是一段不可思议的时光
It's just been such a magical time.
我真希望我能够访问世界上每个国家
And I wish I could have visited every country in the whole world.
你知道吗？ 连新西兰我都想去
You know? Even New Zealand.
听说人们现在都把我和尼克松比较 对吗？
People are now comparing me to Nixon, I heard, right?
-他们不是说的你的样貌 -不 不 不 我也不是说外貌
- They didn't mean your looks. - No, no, no, I don't mean that.
但是 我接受这种比较
But, I mean, I'll take the comparison.
那么 我们从哪儿谈起呢？
So where would you like to begin?
嗯 我也不太清楚最近都发生了什么
Well, I don't really know what's happened lately
因为我被锁在
because I've been locked in a
酒店房间 与外界隔绝里
hotel room without access to the outside world.
当然 你知道我们需要做什么吗？
Of course. You know what we need to do?
我们需要给Leon拿些剪报
We need to get Leon some of the press clippings.
我想他会想看看的
I think he'd like to see some of those.
-是不是得先看看他的食物准备好了没有 -是的
- Should I check on his food first? - Yes.
-不 不 给他拿剪报 -好的
- No, no, get him the press clippings. - Yeah.
首先 和以色列的会谈进展的非常棒
First of all, the talks in Israel went so well
以至于我把到这儿的时间推迟了一天
that I was delayed a day getting here.
然后 这边的会谈也非常棒
And then the talks here were just amazing.
我想弄清楚 您推迟了一天到这儿
So, just to clarify, you were delayed by a day.
-是的 -释放我的时间也推迟了一天
- Yeah. - My release was delayed by a day.
嗯 嗯
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
剪报在这里
Here's those press clippings.
我想让你做的是去看看Leon的食物准备好了没有
What I would like you to do is check on Leon's food.
-因为我知道你饥肠辘辘了 -好的
- 'Cause I know you're hungry. - Yeah.
-Ben 醒醒 -Gary 你为什么给我那些安眠药？
- Ben, wake up. - Gary, why are you giving me all that Ambien?
-Mike Mike 我是Mike -Mike Mike
- Mike. Mike. It's Mike. - Mike. Mike.
副总统那边有麻烦了
We got a problem with the vice president.
好的 呃 等下…… 我马上回来
Okay, um, hang... I'll be right back.
-我不知道发生了什么 -当然
- I don't know what this is all about. - Sure.
-什么事？ -女士 Liz Kerrigan
- What's going on? - Ma'am, Liz Kerrigan
发表了一篇报道说Doyle有不满
is running a story that Doyle is unhappy.
我要不要去看看
Should I go and see if there's
媒体专机上有没有关于这事的闲言？
any chatter about this on the press plane?
老天 还是数据泄漏的原因
Christ, it's that data fuck.
不是 我也不知道 是
No. I don't know. Yes.
就当作我不知道吧
Let's just go with I don't know.
行了 都别往那边看 Leon在看着呢
Okay, please nobody look, but Leon's watching.
好吧 那么你进去 分散他的注意力
Okay, so just go in there and distract him.
必要的话你给他撸一下
Give him a handjob if you have to,
把这事解决了 好吗？
just get it done, okay?
哇 被扣押了两周
Wow, two weeks detained.
真是艰难啊
That is hard.
-我一直在酒店 所以也不是那么糟 -哦 不
- I was in a hotel, so it wasn't that bad. - Oh, no.
Leon开始认为他被推迟一天释放
Leon is starting to think that his release was delayed by a day
是因为我到这儿推迟了一天
because my arrival here was delayed by a day.
他会想明白 是我们直到现在才同意他被释放
He's gonna figure out that we didn't okay his release till now
然后就这件事他会写些不好的报道
and then he'll write something bad about that.
-那就糟了 -是的
- That could be bad. - Yeah.
-现在情况也很糟糕 -是很糟糕了
- That is bad. - It is bad.
Leon想说点什么坏话
And Leon wanting to say it's bad
真的很糟糕 是更糟糕
is really bad. It's worse.
好吧 听着 Ben 七秒钟后 你进去
Okay, look, in seven seconds, you come in there, Ben,
你抓住我的头发把我拽出来
you grab me by the hair and you drag me out,
行吗？ 你在听吗？
okay? Are you listening?
-在听 -好的
-  Yeah. - Okay.
我们得查出来这个Doyle的报道是从哪儿来的
We got to find out where this Doyle story is coming from.
我去媒体专机打听打听
I'll check out the press plane.
你一定很累了
You must be very tired.
你需要休息一下吗?
Would you like to put a pin in this for a moment?
一些人可能会认为美国政府
Some people might think that the american government
扣留了一个美国记者
Detaining an american journalist
这样就有可能出现一些影响不好的照片
So that you can have a photo op might look bad.
你明白吗?
Can you see that?
-Leon 我尊重你这样的记者 -谢谢
- Leon, I respect you so much as a journalist. - Thank you.
当Ben和我首次讨论和平会谈时
And when ben and I were first discussing the peace talks,
我和他说:"Ben Ben 我"
I said to ben, I said, "Ben. Ben, I--"
女士 是国务部
Ma'am, state department.
我必须接这个电话 不好意思 你好? 从不消停 对吧?
This I've got to take. Excuse me. Hello? Never stops, does it?
-Leon 你需要休息 -嗯
- Leon, you need to rest. - Mm-hmm.
我只打了个盹 但我感觉自己棒棒哒
I just had one second of sleep and I feel great.
好 媒体专机上的人们
Okay, maybe the guys in the
可能更希望我到那去
press plane would like me to go over there
告诉他们 美国政府在伊朗关押了一个记者
And tell them about the us government imprisoning a guy in iran.
去媒体专机上把Mike找来
Go get mike from the press plane.
喵了个蠢货 对
Fucking idiots. Yeah.
我们得把他当作人质
We've got to hold him hostage here.
你明白吗? 我们要起飞了
Do you understand? We've got to take off now.
Mike和Gary都不在飞机上
Mike and gary are off the plane.
我们机上有飞行员对吧?
We have a pilot on the plane, right?
好 那我们走吧 我们得出发了
Okay, so let's go. We've got to go.
Leon 你得坐下了
Leon, you've got to sit down.
我晕机的 我需要人抱抱
I'm a bad flier and I might need somebody to hold me.
你这是要再次扣留我吗?
Are you seriously detaining me again?
我是被抛弃了么?
Am I being rendered?
不 你被拉到我方阵营了
No, you're being friendered.
所以你不接收 也得接收我们的热情好客
So just please accept our compulsory hospitality.
天啊 那衣服
Oh, jesus, that suit.
我的妈 你就像个中学老师
My gosh, you look like a middle-school teacher.
好吧 那是Erica
Okay, that's erica. She's
她会带你出去买几件像样的衣服
gonna take you out and buy you some real suits.
而不是你穿的这些政府职员套装
Not these government-issued rags you're wearing.
她不是政府职员 对吧?
She's not exactly government-issue herself, is she?
-对 嘿 别想打她主意 -哦
- Yeah. Hey, don't even look at her. - Oh.
开玩笑啦 我在开玩笑吗?
I'm kidding. Or am I?
哈? 不 确切说 我是在开玩笑啦 Dan
Huh? No, seriously, I'm just fucking with you, dan.
听着 今晚我们
So listen, tonight we're
会让你以一个政治评论员的形象上电视
gonna put you on tv as a political commentator.
-好! -呃?
-Yes! - Yeah?
电视上终于有点好看的节目了
Finally, something good to watch on the idiot box.
我们刚开始进行糖衣樱桃的游说活动
We've just started lobbying for glace cherries,
所以你要提下糖衣樱桃
So mention glace cherries.
好吧 我怎样才能在政治圆桌中
Well, how do I work in
强行插入糖衣樱桃呢?
glace cherries into a political roundtable?
车到山前必有路 听着 如果你帮我弄到糖衣樱桃
You'll figure it out. Listen, you give me glace cherries,
我会给你一床的钞票和妹纸
And I'll give you a bed of money with pussy on the nightstand.
也许能帮你弄到Erica 但不是刚刚那个
Maybe erica. But not her.
不 但也有可能
No. But maybe.
我们就留点悬念吧
we'll just let that hang.
对 我知道 随时待命哦 兄弟
Yeah, yeah. I know. Stay on your toes, buddy.
就像你一直在这里一样
It's gonna be like that the entire time you're here.
看 那是空军一号
Hey, that's air force one.
我的妈 发生什么事了?
Oh, my god. What the hell is happening?
为什么我们被落在这里? 开始打仗了吗?
Why are they leaving us? Are we at war?
在这里开战? 天啊 不 这不可能 不可能
Is it here? Sweet jesus. No, it can't be. It can't be.
-耶稣 -别说耶稣了 闭嘴
-Oh, sweet jesus. - Stop saying jesus. Stop it!
我是这么想的
This is how I see it.
美国政府在计划一次秘密访问
I say the us is planning a secret trip.
伊方要求你们承认这次秘密访问
The iranians ask you to confirm the secret trip.
你否认了秘密访问 因为这是个机密
You say there's no secret trip because it's a secret.
他们以为我是007 于是就扣押了我
They think I'm james bond and detain me.
Leon 你他喵的才不是007
Leon, you're no fucking james bond.
记者都爱编故事
Journalism is storytelling.
你说的是关于的你的勇气 正直
You tell your story about your bravery, your integrity
以及我们如何营救你 给你温暖的故事
And how we rescued you and gave you warm nuts.
伊方是因为你才扣押我的
The iranians detained me because of you.
这就是我的故事
That's my story.
就因为你我被多扣留了一天
They detained me an extra day because of you.
这是我另一个故事
That's my other story.
你这个不知好歹的杂种 还想被救吗?
Now, you want to be rescued or not, you ungrateful shit?
因为总统想凭释放一个美国人上头条
My release was delayed because the president
我就被延迟释放了
Wanted to grab the headlines for freeing an american,
所以她不是故意不释放这个美国人
An american she deliberately did not de-detain.
Jonah 要么把Leon的妈妈喊来空军基地
Jonah, either get leon's mom to the air base
要么就给你自己买个像样点的假发
Or buy yourself a very convincing wig.
-Kent呢? -我母鸡啊
- Where's kent? - I don't know.
可能他关掉了自己的追踪器
Maybe he's bitten off his tracking device.
他现在应该到了才对 这不对劲啊
He should be here by now. This is not okay.
-Mike -Sue 把黄丝带弄断
- Mike. - Break out the yellow ribbon, sue.
我们滞留在伊朗了 Sue 我好怕怕
We are stranded in iran. I'm really scared, sue.
Gary 拿出点男子汉气概 别那么娘
Man up, gary. Or at least lady down a bit.
Gary和Mike被落在伊朗了
Gary and mike have been left behind in iran.
棒极了 简直是搞笑版的黑鹰堕落
Wonderful. It's "Black hawk down" With laurel and hardy.
Amy 如果被问起 别说有人落在伊朗
Amy, if anyone asks, no one's been left behind in iran.
你来了 你刚去哪了?
There you are. Where have you been?
我等你等到胡子都长出来了
I grew a small beard here.
Bill 我已经从慢慢走到快步走了
Bill, of my various walking paces, I selected moderate to fast.
媒体都说副总统对总统不满
The press are saying that the vp is unhappy with the president.
-这可不妙 -是因为地下民意调查吗?
- That doesn't make me happy. - Because of the secret polling?
还是因为他听说
Or because he's heard that
有人黑了去世孩童的资料?
someone has hacked the data of dead children?
或者还有更糟糕的原因?
Or a third reason which is even worse than those?
我们只好钻进Doyle脑袋里 看看他知道什么
We've got to get inside doyle's head, find out what he knows.
-出去 -不 请进 你俩出去
- Get out. - No, come in. You get out.
Mike 你为啥打给我?
Mike, why exactly are you calling me?
-Sue 我们该怎么办? -那里有一架备用飞机
- What do we do, sue? - There's a backup plane.
找到备用机
Find the backup plane.
快走 我的妈 备用机在哪里?
Come on! Oh, my god. Where is it?
我不知道! 妈蛋!
I don't know! Oh, shit!
-不好意思噜 不好意思噜 -那是法语
- Pardonne. Pardonne. - That's french!
噢 我是来错地方了么?
Ooh, am I in the wrong place?
-这里是QVC电视购物公司么? -Amy
- Is this qvc? - Amy.
唔... 听说你在游说Sidney Purcell
Hmm. Hear you're lobbying with sidney purcell now.
那个梦想假期是
The man whose dream vacation is hunting
狩猎里约街头小孩的人
The street kids of rio on a human safari.
没有游说 不 那不合法
Not lobbying. No, that'd be illegal.
我是个咨询顾问 而且我必须说
I'm a consultant. And I gotta say, I like the guy
在他告诉我未来的我有多富有后 我就更喜欢他了
A hell of a lot more ever since he told me how rich I'm gonna be.
对你被炒鱿鱼的事感到抱歉 你工作才刚上手
Sorry you got fired. You were almost good at your job,
而且做得挺出众的
Which really made you stand out.
彼此彼此
Right back at you.
直播的时候 我们就不能对彼此这么友善了
Can't be this nice to each other on air, you know.
我懂 愿最好的人获胜
Oh, I know. May the best man win.
那就是我 那应该是我
And that'll be me. Which will be me.
Mike! Mike!
我找到备用客机了 快过来
I found the backup plane. Come on.
感谢天感谢地
Thank god.
我从来没那么喜欢飞机
I've never had strong feelings for a plane,
但现在我愿意为那家伙劈腿wendy
But right now I would cheat on wendy with that thing.
Jonah 我们得谈谈
Jonah, we need to talk.
我们现在和leon west的妈妈在车上
We are just in the car with leon west's mother.
女士 你需要什么吗？
Do you need anything, ma'am?
不 不用 谢谢
No, I'm good. Thank you.
好的
Great.
Jonah 我知道副总统办公室出事儿了
Jonah, I know something's happening at the vp's office.
哦 对 你当然知道
Oh. Okay, you do.
你得告诉我出了什么事
I need you to tell me what's going on.
呃 非得现在告诉你吗?
And, uh, do I have to tell you that right now?
对 是的
Yes, you do.
我觉得我们可以停下来喝杯咖啡
I was thinking we could stop for a coffee.
呃 Teddy一直在摸我
Uh, teddy's been touching me.
或者喝茶
Or tea.
呃 等我消化一会
Uh, just processing that.
等等 Davison先生?
Wait, mr. Davison?
妈的 你开免提了?
Shit, am I on speakerphone?
对不起  jonah 到底发生什么?
Sorry, jonah, what happened exactly?
呃 嗯 他--
Um, well, he--
他-- 他攥住了我的蛋蛋
He-- he cupped my testicles.
之前有一次 他抚摸了
On another occasion, he patted
或者说轻弹了我的蛋蛋
Or tapped on my testicles.
然后还有一次
And then on another occasion,
他紧握住我的蛋蛋相当久的一段时间
He held my testicles for a significantly long time.
猜怎么着 我刚订婚了
Guess what. I just got engaged.
你他妈的在逗我?Catherine也在那？
Are you fucking kidding me? Catherine's there, too?
嗨 jonah Jason向我求婚 我同意了
Hi, jonah. Jason proposed and I said yes.
好吧 妈蛋 祝贺你
Well, shit, congratulations.
婚姻是美好的 这是个很好的制度
Marriage is good. It's a fine institution.
别告诉我妈妈 我要给她个惊喜
Don't tell my mom. I want to surprise her.
Jonah 你还有啥想告诉我们的吗?
Jonah, is there anything else you want to tell us?
我不知道 屋子里还有谁？
I don't know. Is there anybody else in the room?
只有我和Bill了
Just myself and bill again.
还有我在做记录 Sue也在?！艹！
And I'm here taking notes. Sue's there?! Fuck!
好了 够了 不 我没啥可说的了
Okay, well, no. There's nothing else that I have to say.
我很确信我是
I'm pretty sure that I'm
唯一一个被teddy摸过的人 行了吧？
the only one that teddy's been touching, okay?
多谢了 朋友们 聊得真愉快
Thanks, guys. Great talk.
好了 我们除了这好笑的故事啥也没打听到
Okay, we got nothing out of that but a funny story.
飞机坏了 我们不能起飞
Plane's broken. We can't take off.
他们说还需要一周才能修好
They said it's gonna be a week until they get the part.
天了噜 人家大天朝子民能在一周内
Jesus christ, the chinese can 3-d print
用3d打印出一百栋房子!尼玛!
A hundred houses in that time. Fuck!
Mike 你说为啥不给备用飞机再准备个备用飞机?
Why isn't there a backup plane for the backup plane, mike?
我们得去坐媒体专用飞机
We need to get on the press plane.
媒体们恨咱们 尤其你
The press hates us, especially you.
他们受不了你 Gary 我们有酒
They can't stand you. We have booze, gary.
他们对酒没有抵抗力
And they have a crippling dependency.
啥 这能行吗?在一个干燥的国家
What, is this gonna work? In a dry country,
有酒的人说了算
The man with all the booze holds the cards.
什么事?
yeah?
夫人 真的有电话找你
Ma'am, you actually do have a phone call.
哦 是kent和bill 开了免提
Oh. It's kent and bill on speaker.
嘿 同志们 啥事?
Hey, guys, what's up?
夫人 我们担心Doyle可能知道投票的事了
Ma'am, we're worried that doyle knows about the polling.
什么投票?Kent
What polling? Kent.
我认为有必要观察一下
I thought it might be
Doyle作为副总统是怎么表现的
useful to see how doyle is performing as veep.
我特意向Doyle保证不会那么做 Kent
I specifically promised doyle that I would not do that, kent.
抱歉 但这确实带来了有趣的结果
I apologize. But it did throw up some very interesting results.
但我还是等你没那么生气的时候再告诉你
But I will run those by you at a less angry time.
我们想了一个自认为很机智的计划
We have what we think is a very smart plan of action.
挺牛逼的 相当牛逼
It's brilliant. Quite brilliant.
我们告诉Doyle你的竞选活动
We tell doyle that your campaign
利用丢失的数据筛选出丧子的父母作为目标
Used stolen data to target bereaved parents.
你他妈到底为啥要
Why in the name of pixelated fuck
这么做?我的神呐！
Would you do that? My god!
还有说这事的时候你能不能用暗号?
And can you please use code when we're talking about this?
用个什么词 比如说 用 纸杯蛋糕 代替 数据
Use the word, I don't know, cupcake instead of data
用 幸福 代替 丧子 之类的
And use happy instead of bereaved or something.
这样做能把他拉来我们这边 影响他
It binds him to us. Infects him.
而且他办公室那边
And elements of his office
被抄送了提到违规的邮件
were cc'd on e-mails mentioning the breach.
没错 这起盗用去世孩子的蛋糕事件后
Exactly, he will be as involved as the rest of us
他会和我们其他人一样
In targeting happy parents after stealing cupcakes
被卷入幸福父母的筛选事件
About their dead children.
好吧
fine.
向他注入幸福小蛋糕病毒 好吧?
Inject him with the happy cupcake virus, all right?
希望他变肿大然后挂掉
I hope he swells up and dies.
顺便说一句 这不是暗语
That's not code, by the way.
哇 ben 我为啥不知道这里发生了什么?
Wow. Ben, why don't I know what's going on here?
我不知道 我本该是掌握大权按钮的
I don't know. I'm supposed to have my finger on the button.
但目前看来 按钮的电线换了新接头
But for all I know, it's been rewired
我现在只能在某个柜子的小角落里控制什么小灯泡
And I'm just operating some sort of light in a closet somewhere.
我们要把Leon怎么处置?
And what are we gonna do about leon?
我要对他像亲哥哥一样
I'm gonna treat him like my own brother, ahem,
那个哥哥在86年被我杀掉了
Who I had murdered back in '86.
总统在中东很受欢迎
The president is charming the middle east.
但显然她的副总统对她不满意?
But apparently her own vp is unhappy with her?
假的 难道我们要讨论谣言了吗?
Not true. And we're discussing rumors?
这是新闻台还是寝室卧谈会?
Is this a news channel or a dorm room?
你可以认为总统的伊朗行
You could say that the president's iran visit
是把一个美味的糖衣樱桃
Puts a delicious glace
放在了selina meyer之旅的蛋糕上
cherry on the cake of selina meyer's tour.
嗯 欢迎从荒原回来
Well, welcome back from the wasteland.
为咱俩干杯 为你漂亮的完成任务干杯
Here's to us. To a job well done on your part.
你很棒 当然 我知道
You were great. Yeah, I know.
你知道么 我们依旧可以做得很棒
You know, we could still be great.
我们能吗?
We could?
哦 是
Oh, yeah.
能问你个问题吗?问吧
Can I ask you something? Uh-oh.
我那么容易被看透吗?真的吗？
Am I that transparent? Really?
Dan 你确实有点
Dan, you kind of are.
好吧 Amy
Well, amy,
如果你能让我进白宫
I would love it if you would give me
我会很开心的
Access to the white house.
哦
Oh.
什么?
What?
你以为我要问别的事?
You think I was gonna ask you something else?
不 好的
No. Okay.
喂? Amy 噩耗
Yeah? Amy, bad news.
Ericsson 告诉Doyle我们竞选利用了
Ericsson told doyle that the campaign used
死掉的孩子的数据来筛选最近丧子的父母选民
Dead kids' data to target recently bereaved parents.
天了噜 这简直是蓄意自我破坏行为
God, that is some elaborate self-sabotage right there.
是太阳马戏团的自杀式炸弹袭击
That is cirque du soleil suicide bombing.
坐时光机回去 阻止这件事发生
Go back in time and stop that from happening.
你没事吧?
You okay?
感觉我像是在靠呼吸机维持生命
I feel like I'm on a life-support machine
然后他们不停地拔插销下来 给手机充电
And they keep pulling the plug to charge their phones.
要龙舌兰么?好啊
Tequila? Yeah.
- 妈妈咪呀 太吓人了 - 冷静点 Gary
-My god, this is so scary. -Quiet down, Gary.
- 我就是受到了惊吓嘛 - 赶紧的 给我冷静点儿--
-It's just really scary. -Hurry up and be quiet--
- 哦 天哪 - 哦 你在逗我吗
-oh, my god. -Oh, you're kidding.
- 神啊 哦 上帝 - 快捡起来!
-Jesus. Oh, my god. -Pick them up!
我可不想在这儿蹲监狱
I don't want to go to jail over here.
我们现在只有大概10秒钟的时间 不仅要全喝掉这些
We've got about 10 seconds to drink everything
还要吃掉这些瓶子
And then eat the bottles.
你要见我 夫人?
You wanted to see me, ma'am?
哦 我打扰到你休息了?
Oh, did I wake you up?
呃 没有
Um, no.
进来 进来 赶紧的
Come in. Come in, come in.
伙计 你脸色不大好呀
You don't look good, man.
你看起来就像是机舱失了压
You look like the cabin depressurized
你马上就要昏迷了似的
And you fell into a coma or something.
- 不 我--我很好 - 坐吧 坐下
-No, I'm-- I'm fine. -Sit. Sit.
所以...
so...
有什么事儿啊 夫人?
What's up, ma'am?
我现在掌控不了局势了 Ben 我真的很无力
I'm not in control, Ben. I'm really not.
- 怕啥 我们有专门的飞行员 - 你知道我在说什么
-Well, we have pilots for that. -You know what I mean.
Leon  Kent的投票
Leon, Kent's polling,
烤在杯蛋糕里的死去的孩子
Dead kids baked in the cupcakes.
所有的这些都让我坚信
So all of this has confirmed for me
我做出拉点新人进来的决定
That I made the right decision
是正确的
When I decided to bring in somebody else.
那太棒了 众人拾柴火焰高嘛
That's great. More minds the merrier.
好像是有这么一句话吧 我猜的
That's a saying, I think.
并没有 她的名字是 Karen Collins
No, I don't think it is. Her name is Karen Collins.
好咩? 想想我那些当律师的旧时光 你可能会记起来她
Okay? You might remember her from my old lawyering days.
不 我是说 我很认真的哦 Ben
No. I mean, seriously, Ben,
她拥有我求之不得的一切
She's everything that I'm missing.
她聪慧 有才干 做事有条有理
She's smart, she's capable, she's organized.
她听起来就像是...
She sounds like the...
全能工具包
Complete package.
哦 不 不 我是说 你别误解了我的意思
Oh, no, no. But, I mean, you know, don't misunderstand me.
因为 怎么说呐 我真的真的很尊重你 Ben
Because, I mean, obviously I so respect you, Ben,
而且你真的是一个特别能干的人
And I think you're incredibly capable.
同时我也觉得你--
And I also think that you--
Ben?
马里兰安德鲁斯空军基地
我需要见总统 因为我要做汇报以及汇报背景预告
I need to see the president for a debrief and a prebrief.
回去排队啊 Cary Grant 好吗? 副总统已经预约了第一位了
Back off, Cary Grant, okay? Vice president is first up.
- 不 - 我需要告诉妈妈我订婚了
-No - I need to tell my mom that I got engaged.
- 哦 我就是和他订婚了 - 是呀 我也订婚了
Oh, also I got engaged. Yeah, so did I.
和她 看出来了吧
To her. That's obvious.
好吧 恭喜 那啥 --听着--听我说
Okay, congrats. And-- listen-- listen up.
一会儿总统下飞机要做的第一件事儿就是
The first thing that's gonna happen once the president lands
做一次汇报 然后我们--
Is a debrief and then we're--
怎么我觉得木有人听我讲话呐?
Why does it feel like nobody is listening to me?
这对你来说太勉强了 是吧?
This is tough for you, huh?
看起来某人需要多学习学习运筹管理的技巧啊
Looks like someone needs to learn some management skills.
不好意思 你特么是哪一位啊?
I'm sorry, who the fuck are you?
哦 我是Karen Collins 新上任的总统高级顾问
Oh, I'm Karen Collins, the president's new senior advisor.
我的专长是--常识
My specialty-- common sense.
我要和我妈咪谈谈
I need to talk to my mom.
哦 我的天 Catherine 瞧瞧你
Oh, my god, Catherine, look at you.
还记得我吗?
Do you remember me?
嗯 当然记得
Of course. Yeah.
我真的需要跟我妈咪谈谈
I really need to talk to my mom.
哦 那我带你去 现在就给你解决这事儿 现在就去
Oh, let's handle it, then. Dive in. Let's dive in.
呃 很显然我事先知道这个Karen要来的事儿
Um, so I obviously knew about this karen.
通知你们了吗?
Were you told?
高级顾问 就是她嘛
Senior advisor, yes.
- 哦 当然 - 当然 就是她呀
-Oh, sure. -Of course. Yeah.
- Amy 你好  - 嗯 怎么了?
- Amy, hey. - Yeah, what?
呃 我们找到了Leon West的妈妈 她看起来 呃...
Um, we have Leon West's mom, and she just looks, um...
非常不好
Just very terrible.
我-- 这事儿和-- 和Karen说
I-- talk to this-- talk to Karen.
呃 她的专长是常识
Um, her specialty is common sense.
没错 记性真好
That's right. Good memory.
- 我是Jonah Ryan - 很高兴见到你 我是Karen
- I'm Jonah Ryan. - Pleasure to meet you. I'm Karen.
Sue 如果有人问起我
Sue, if anybody asks for me,
就说我去外面的夜色深处里尖叫了
I've gone outside to scream into the night.
m 16 2 l 3 8 l 12 8 l 12 6 l 16 6 m 33 -5 l 37 8 l 42 8 m 29 -12 l 21 -12 l 24 -10 l 24 6 l 23 8 l 30 8 l 25 -5 l 27 -10 l 31 -10 m -15 -5 l -23 8 l -7 8 m -9 -12 l 12 -12 l 2 -8 l 2 -4 l 13 -9 l 15 -7 l 2 -1 l 2 2 l 16 -4 l 16 -2 l 2 4 l 1 6 m -11 -24 l 15 -24 l 15 -22 l 1 -22 l 1 -16 l 11 -16 l 11 -19 l 25 -19 l 28 -15 l -11 -15 m -20 -22 l -24 -15 l -20 -15 m -26 -12 l -21 -12 l -32 6 l -33 6 l -33 8 l -39 8
好吧
Okay.
m 0 0 l 0 -13 l -18 -13 l -18 0
2014年7月，美国《华盛顿邮报》
驻伊朗德黑兰分社社长贾森·芮塞恩
（Jason Rezaian）与同为记者的
妻子萨利希（Yeganeh Salehi）一
起被伊朗政府逮捕。当地时间2015
年4月20日，芮塞恩的律师莱拉·阿
赫桑首次获准与其会面，从而得知
芮塞恩被指控包括间谍罪在内的4
项罪名，称其收集并向图谋不轨者
提供“内部和外交政策”相关信息。
把我那份儿也叫出来吧
Have one for me, too.
你休息好了吗?
Did you rest?
我睡得跟死猪似的
I slept like a drugged log.
很好 我看起来怎么样啊?
Good. How do I look?
很疲惫
Very tired.
你要知道 Gary通常就会粉饰得很好
You know, Gary usually sugarcoats that.
疲惫?
Tired?
老天
God.
刚才我的眼皮抽了一下吗?
Did my eye just twitch?
没有
No.
嘿 Catherine 关于先前
Hey, Catherine, about earlier.
- 调戏那事儿 - 什么?
- The molesting. -What?
嗯?
Hmm?
等等 什么玩意儿?
Wait, what?
嘿 看 你妈妈下来了
Hey, look, there's your mom.
这不仅仅是关系到我
This isn't just about me.
这是关系到这两个...
This is about the strength of these two...
美丽的人儿的权益
Beautiful people.
在人类历史长河中 我能尽到的绵薄之力
I am most humbled to have played my small part
实在是沧海一粟
In human history.
Wendy 我到不了小别墅了
I'm not gonna make it to the cottage, Wendy.
我在伊朗
I'm in iran.
事实证明 你不能用小型瓶的
Turns out you can't buy a
威士忌去换一张登机牌
boarding pass with tiny bottles of jack daniels.
- 哇哦 棒极了 -不 是吗?
- Wow, that was great. - Wasn't it?
- 很多人要和你谈话 - 好的 我知道了
- A lot of people need to talk to you. - Okay, that's fine.
- 妈咪 - Catherine!
- Mom. - Catherine!
- 我们订婚了 - 不 你没有
- We're engaged. - No, you're not.
- 是的 我们就是订婚了 - 对啊 我们已经订婚了
- Yes, we are. - But we are.
我可是48岁的聪明人
I'm 48.
放开你的咸猪手
Put your hand down.
- 嗯 你能回来真好 夫人 - 嗯
- Well, it's nice to have you back, ma'am. - Yeah.
- 那么... - Karen!
- And so... - Karen!
- 我在这儿 - 我要给你个大拥抱
- I'm here. - I'm gonna give you a hug.
好啦 见到你真好
All right. Great to see you.
见到你真好呀
I'm so glad to see you.
- 你们相互认识了吗? - 嗯
- You guys met?  - Yes.
- 太好了 真棒 - 无可挑剔
- Great. Great. - Besties.
我们离开这个柏油路面去别的地方吧
Let's get off the tarmac.
我没有吃小吃 我可是在节食呢
I'm not snacking. I'm on my diet.
我在吃芹菜杆
It's a celery stick.
好吧好吧 我在吃曲奇饼
All right, it's a cookie.
我每天都吃枣
I've had dates every day.